MD ATIKUJJAMAN

3 Gearing Close, SW17 6DJ, Totting, London

+44 7359 208450 | Mdatikujaman81@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/md-atikujjaman-5a7a78232 | https://atik81.github.io/#portfolio | https://github.com/atik81

PROFILE

I am a passionate front-end developer with a love for creating beautiful and interactive websites. I have a strong foundation in JavaScript, HTML, and CSS, allowing me to bring designs to life and provide engaging user experiences. Additionally, my knowledge of SQL enables me to work with databases effectively. also have experience with Python and basic familiarity with C# and C++.

EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS

Roehampton University - London \mid Completed the second year at Roehampton University Computer Science \mid September 2021 - Current

- Computer Systems - Computing and Society - Database - Mathematics for Computer

Science - Software Development 1 - Software Development 2 - Algorithm - Operating

System - Software Development 3 - Software Engineering - Data Science - Artificial Intelligence

Kingston University - London | International foundation year in computing Science, Engineering, and Computing | Passed with overall 70% | February 2021 - July 2021

Module: Applied mathematics - pure mathematics - computing and foundation academic English skills

Baf shaheen college - Shamshernagar, Sylhet, Bangladesh - Higher Secondary Certificate Gpa: $5 \mid April \ 2017 - April \ 2019$

Subject: Bangla, English, mathematics, physics, chemistry, ICT, higher mathematics.

KEY SKILLS

C#: IntermediateC++: IntermediateMS Office: Expert

SQL: Expert

HTML: AdvancedPython: ExpertCSS: AdvancedJAVA SCRIPT: Expert

WORK EXPERIENCE

Healthcare Advisor | Boots Pharmacy | November 2021 to Present

21-23 St John's Road, London

In Charge of the store and all till systems opening and closing.

- I advise customers about medicine and other's boots product. Virtually help customers and other advisors with online orders, product or service inquiries over the phone and the Boots website
- Smoothly processed incoming online orders and booked store goods. Effective contribution of sales target.
- Responsible for meeting, greeting, sales plan, restocking the shelves
- · when inventory runs low and helping customers check out and providing
- prominent levels of Customer service.

Waiter | Akash Tandoori | July 2021 to November 2021

70 Northcote Rd, London

- In charge of all business activities, sales, and client relations
- Served up to 85 guests each evening while smooth processing
- Incoming orders and managing over 200 Transactions every evening.

Sales assistant | The Food & Drink store | March 2021 to July 2021

Tooting Bec Road, London

- Guiding customers to the items they need.
- · Refilling the supermarket shelves as items run out and helping
- · customers check out.

Languages:

•Bengali : Fluent

•English: Fluent

Hindi : Intermediate

•Urdu : Beginner

Projects:

- Personal portfolio: This is my website. I made this website with HTML, CSS, and JAVASCRIPT.
- Vaccum cleaner with Python: I made Vaccum clean with Python code. First, I create an environment for clean and dirt areas. Users can choose the auto or manual option for clean dirt areas.

Map For City Distance:

- I made this project with Python for my University coursework. First, I create a map and I use three algorithms for finding the shortest road. I use speech Recognition for this code.
- Website For countries: I made this project with Html, CSS, SQL, JAVASCRIPT, and DOCKERFILE. From this project, users can find out about regions, the country's populations, the country's city, and capital city.